<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Category1 on Frank&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chenjs1986.github.io/categories/category1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Category1 on Frank&#39;s Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Frank&#39;s Blog</title>
      <url>https://chenjs1986.github.io/images/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://chenjs1986.github.io/images/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.133.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Frank Chen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://chenjs1986.github.io/categories/category1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build a web server </title>
      <link>https://chenjs1986.github.io/posts/web-1.build-a-web-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chenjs1986.github.io/posts/web-1.build-a-web-server/</guid>
      <description>If you have much data and often need to share with colleagues, I recommend you to set up a web server and design some online websites for needer to get.
Maybe someone has a question, to build a web server seems difficult, why don’t find other solutions?
I really try to do but it’s not easy. I once tried output data to RPT documents and transferred to others, but it’ll spend myself too much time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to do with R?</title>
      <link>https://chenjs1986.github.io/posts/r-1.-what-i-to-do-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chenjs1986.github.io/posts/r-1.-what-i-to-do-with-r/</guid>
      <description>R is a very famous programming language. R was designed by statisticians who want analysis to be easy.
We can use R to analyze data or formal digraph. I usually take some graph by R. As you know, many tasks are very similar in our work and we must do them again and again just because some data is changed. It will spend our much time and it’s very boring. But if you have R, you can do this easily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IFRS17-introduce </title>
      <link>https://chenjs1986.github.io/posts/irfs17-1.introduce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chenjs1986.github.io/posts/irfs17-1.introduce/</guid>
      <description>What is IFRS17? Ifrs17 is an international accounting standard for insurance contracts. It&amp;rsquo;s very difficult. Since the standard was pubilshed, there are many discussion about it. Many people welcomed it ,mean while others didn&amp;rsquo;t like it. WHY? The standard let insurance company clarify it&amp;rsquo;s profit how constitute. so for users , like investors , the profit will be very clear and let investors be more easy to take decisions. But for insurance companies, it will spend their much time to prepare for reports.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
